Hi everyone and welcome to this new video here. Today I'm going to show you
something special. Luxury BDSM toys from the brand called Upko. I first saw the
Upko items at the Boutique Bizarre in Hamburg and already there I was
fascinated by the product design and the packaging. So I'm really happy about this
cooperation thanks very much to upko and i also have a discount code for you guys just check out
the description text i'm already wearing one of the pieces this corset but i also have a whip
and two really cool gecks both are a bit special i think you've probably not seen one of these so far
But I'll tell you more about them later because first I'm going to complete my outfit with
a beautiful choker with a special gimmick.
And I mean check out this packaging, it's all so beautiful and so high quality.
I'm completing the choker because I'm adding some letters to it.
So it's spelling my name in the end.
So you can basically write what you want on it and add the letters.
And there you go.
I think it looks super cute and the big bonus point here is that the colors match exactly.
This gold metal tone is the same as here on the corset and on the eyelets in the back.
And also the corset has a really nice decorative stitching here.
So from OOPKO you get the whole package, accessories, outfits, restraints and also gags.
And I'm going to show you the first one now.
So this is the ball gag.
Basically a normal ball gag although it feels really nice and with the leather parts and
also the gold matches again.
And we have the 3D rose here, which I can simply insert into the ball gag.
And now you have a completely different look.
Now it's full of lip gloss.
But you get the idea.
So you have like this multi-piece and multi-design gag here.
Let me check.
It's also easy to detach the rose again.
And then you have the normal ball gag again.
So this is really something new.
I haven't seen this anywhere so far.
And I also seen a lot of pictures with this ball gag because it looks just so beautiful.
And also the product pictures from Okko, they're so high class.
And you can't really tell that this is like BDSM items and BDSM stuff because it's just presented in such an elegant way.
I haven't unpacked it yet but this is a whip.
Hello beautiful. This is the leather thorn whip and the top part here is
shaped like a rose again so like the ball gag and also the metal has the same
color again than the other metal parts so design 100% one line the vision of opco and i really
liked it is bdsm is not vulgar and sex deserves to be noble and i totally agree with that i'm so
sick of seeing all these bdsm articles presented in such a slobby and bad way so opco has a really
nice philosophy with all the high quality presenting and all the really
high quality parts this is such a lightweight and I'm really not an expert
doing this there is the name again engraved here at the end so it's really
thought through design and it looks really good together and the set here
with the other pieces. Imagine if you want to introduce your girlfriend or
your boyfriend into the world of BDSM toys and you go online to buy your first
ball gag at a online adult store and you get something like this which looks
really gross to be honest and a bit disgusting and then you have something
like this which you can present to your girlfriend as a gift and it looks like
BDSM meets designer items I don't know it's just really beautiful so there's no
question which the shoes I guess and also everything comes with a really nice
back I would say that this comes a bit of a revolution to the scene because
it's an invisible mouth gag and it took me a while to understand how it works so
I hope I can explain it to you properly now okay let's get this out of here
without damaging everything no it's really easy
this is the gag and it may not look like a gag at the first moment but the idea
behind us that you insert these pieces
let me check this way around like this into your mouth between your teeth and
so it prevents the teeth from being closed again and you have to leave your
mouth open okay let's try it
of course you have to close it in the back so
i think it's really unique that you have nothing in the front of your mouth
when you're wearing this kind of gag and that is also
yeah something it makes it visually appealing
I guess because you don't really see it and
of course this is not something for the extreme BDSM
been there done that person but something for
people starting to get to know the topic or just want to
have something playful and to experience
the scene and the items a bit. Okay I've shown you one two three four five pieces
from UBKO. As I said I have a lot more and you can get the whole product range
BDSM range in their shop. I'll link it down below and I have to emphasize it
again it's so visually appealing all in all really aesthetic I just love how
everything looks and works together and that there is someone who brings the
BDSM world or topic into like this higher quality or visual really elegant
way so I love these products I'm really glad that I could show them to you I
hope you like them too and that you maybe switch your old gross ballgat to
something like this yeah what else can I say I I'm just in love with these
products and the whole brand image has any one of you ever heard of the
invisible mouth gag so far or do you already own it and then tell me your
experience as I said I saw it in Hamburg and now I can try it myself
yay and i wish you a nice day see you in the next video bye